don't know exactly what to call this but
um
Apple number 51 is online juries not in
actual court cases because that clearly
problems like but in your own life so if
you are fighting with your spouse or
fighting with your friend or even in
custody disputes having a way to give
both sides of your story and have people
weigh in on it and it's not binding in
any way but at least it like helps you I
know I find when I'm if I'm online
giving advice to my friends I'm of
course going to find in their favor
because I'm not an impartial jury but
when you have stranger to say okay like
this is what especially in custody cases
so this is what happened before our when
we were married
here's what happened during the divorce
who do you think should pay whom what
who do you think should get custody of
the kids none anyway but it's like at
least you get that validation like okay
well this Court did kind of screw up I
should have more custody I should have
more no it's just an idea
online jury I think it helps more in
like friendship cases where it's like
okay well my friend more white to my
wedding and here's a picture this it's
like okay well we know that that's not
acceptable and like but wait anyway
having an actual jury that so you can
sit on juries you can ask questions of
them and it would just be fun